<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creme-De-La-Crema on Home</title>
    <link>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creme-De-La-Crema on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Brew</title>
      <link>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>My introduction into the coffee world is probably very similar to anyone born and raised in New England: Dunkin Donuts. The earliest drink I can remember getting from Dunkin was when I was in high school. It was their Hazelnut Coffee Coolata - a blended ice heavy-on-the-quotation-marks “coffee” drink that must’ve been 98% sugar and 2% coffee and/or coffee flavoring, served in an American-large plastic cup with a bright orange and pink straw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Fill out the form below to leave a question, comment, or riddle even. I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as I can.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sip &amp; Learn Coffee Series: Introduction</title>
      <link>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/post/coffee-info-series-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Creme-De-La-Crema.github.io/post/coffee-info-series-intro/</guid>
      <description>Hi friends!
I’m starting a series of blog posts exploring and detailing the life of a coffee bean from Earth’s ground to brewed grounds. I’ll be researching the journey starting on a coffee plantation, continuing through the stages of processing and shipping, all the way through roasting and sales, then finally ending with brewing methods used to enjoy a delicious cup.
My goal is to answer questions that bounce around in my head, as well as answer more basic coffee questions such as: Where and when does coffee grow?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
